eventsbot.com 2016-05-12

# Privacy Policy

|   
---  
  
| ****PRIVACY POLICY  ****  
---  
  
Your privacy is very important to Eventsbot Services Pvt. Ltd. We have developed this Policy for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate, disclose and make use of personal information. eventsbot.com will provide no personal information, including email address or any other contact information, to any third party for any reason. eventsbot.com will only use the provided information for processing of the transaction for which the information was provided. Any further use of information will require an opt-in authorization that must be explicitly and obviously selected by the person providing it.

**Key features of our privacy policy include:**  

  * Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected. 
  * We will collect and use any personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, that too after obtaining the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law. 
  * We will retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes. 
  * We will collect personal information by fair and lawful means, and where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned. 
  * Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it would be used, and to the extent necessary for those purposes only. The information provided should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date. 
  * We will protect personal information through reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification. 
  * Information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information will be made readily available to customers.
